Philip J. Klass Collection 1948-2000 Mss.Ms.Coll.59
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. UFO Case Files, 1948-1993; 5.5 lin. feet
  - Other, 1962-1977 (Box Series II-11)
    - Other: Zond IV-UFO, 1968 (Brad Sparks Challenge), 1962-1977 (Box Series II-11)
    - Other: Zond IV-UFO, 1968 (Marcia Smith Challenge), 1968-1976 (Box Series II-11)
- Series III. UFO Subject files, 1950-1996; 5 lin. feet
  Subject files on UFOs and alien abductions, consisting mostly of newspaper and magazine clippings, opinion pieces, government reports, and some correspondence. Of particular note is the file on the Volunteer Flight Officers Network (VFON) which was created in the mid-1960s by pro-UFOlogist Herbert Roth, a United Airlines employee. The organization was intended to help the North American Aerospace Defense Command (NORAD) refine its computer software for predicting atmospheric reentry of satellites and rockets. Roth secretly hoped VFON might also report UFOs. The file does show that pilot reports of UFOs were greatest during the period public interest, but when interest waned so did pilot reports. The material is semi-unique and may not be available anywhere else unless Roth maintained his own files. The project was ended in the late-1960s when NORAD and United Airlines discontinued funding.
  - Abduction-Hypnosis, 1992-1993 (Box Series III-1)
  - Air and Space Magazine-"When Pilots See UFOs," 1987, 1987-1988 (Box Series III-1)
  - Allen, Woody-"The UFO Menace, 1977 (Box Series III-1)
  - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics-UFOs, 1968-1979 (Box Series III-1)
    - Folder #1, 1968-1972 (Box Series III-1)
    - Folder #2, 1973-1976 (Box Series III-1)
    - UFO Subcommittee, 1968-1979 (Box Series III-1)
  - Austrian UFO Study (Keul et al), 1981-1982 (Box Series III-1)
  - Baker, Robert: "Alien Abductions or Alien Productions?: Some not so Unusual Personal Experiences", 1992 (Box Series III-1)
  - Baker, Robert: "No Aliens, No Abductions: Just Regressive Hypnosis, Waking Dreams, and Anthropomorphism" (Box Series III-1)
  - Bartholomew, Robert: Fantasy-Prone / Abductions, 1991 (Box Series III-1)
  - Blackmore, Susan: Abductions, 1994-1995 (Box Series III-1)
  - Blania-Boxlnar, Zbigniew: "What Was it That Fell at Rosewell? The Same Thing as at Laredo!", n.d. (Box Series III-1)
  - Blum, Ralph: Pro-UFO author, 1974 (Box Series III-1)
  - Boylan, Richard-"Abductionist", 1992-1996 (Box Series III-1)
  - Bryan, C.D.B.: Abductions-Book on Conference at MIT, 1995 (Box Series III-2)
  - Canadian UFO Files, 1950-1967 (Box Series III-2)
  - Carlton University UFO Study-Dr. Nicholas, 1993 (Box Series III-2)
  - CBS-TV: "Intruders" (May 17 and 19, 1992) (Box Series III-2)
  - Center for UFO Studies-Hynek, 1966-1986 (Box Series III-2)
  - Christian Science Monitor Article, 1977 (Box Series III-2)
  - Close Encounters of the Third Kind, 1976 - (Box Series III-2)
  - Condon Report-Comments on, 1966-1986 (Box Series III-2)
  - Crabbe, Anne. Future Problem Solving Program (Coe College), 1982-1983 (Box Series III-3)
  - Crews, Frederic: Review, 1998 (Box Series III-3)
  - Cronkite, Walter-On UFOs, 1976-1977 (Box Series III-3)
  - Educational Publications, 1978-1980 (Box Series III-3)
  - Fisher, Murray-PlayBoxy UFO Article, 1975-1977 (Box Series III-3)
  - Fraser, Alister B.-freak optical effects, 1975 (Box Series III-3)
  - Fry, Daniel W., 1966-1983 (Box Series III-3)
  - Fund for UFO Research, 1979-1984 (Box Series III-3)
  - Genesis of E.T. Appearances, n.d. (Box Series III-3)
  - Goertzel, Ted: "Unusual Personal Experiences": False Memories on UFO Abductions, 1993 (Box Series III-3)
  - Gotlib, Richard-Canadian Abduction Psychiatrist, 1991 (?) (Box Series III-3)
  - Hayes, E. Nelson: "The Smithsonian's Satellite Tracking Program", 1962 (Box Series III-3)
  - Howe, Linda: 1992 Abduction Pictures (Box Series III-3)
  - Huyghe, Patrick: "UFO Files: The Untold Story", 1979 (Box Series III-3)
  - Hynek, J. Allen, 1960-1985 (Box Series III-3)
  - Hynek, J. Allen and CUFOS, 1956-1976 (Box Series III-3)
    - Folder #1, 1956-1967 (Box Series III-3)
    - Folder #2, 1968-1975 (Box Series III-3)
    - Folder #3, 1976 -1983 (Box Series III-4)
  - Hynek, J. Allen: "J. Allen Hyned answers Philip Klass on UFOs", 1975 (Box Series III-4)
  - Iowa Fireball (PJK-8), 1972 (Box Series III-4)
  - Jacobs, David, 1992-1993 (Box Series III-4)
  - Jones, R. V.: "The Natural Philosophy of Flying Saucers", 1968 (Box Series III-4)
  - Jung, C. G.: Flying Saucers (Box Series III-4)
  - Keyhoe, Donald E., 1968-1974 (Box Series III-4)
  - Klass, Philip J., 4 folders (Box Series III-4)
    - MJ-12 Papers, 1987-1990 (Box Series III-4)
    - "That's Entertainment! TV's UFO Coverup, 1996 (Box Series III-4)
    - "UFOs, 'N-Rays' and Pathological Science", 1968 (Box Series III-4)
    - UFO Survey, 1986-1987, 1974-1987 (Box Series III-4)
  - Maccabee, Bruce: "UFOs: Fantasy or Present Reality", 1985 (Box Series III-4)
  - Mack, John, 1991-1995 (Box Series III-4)
  - Mack, John-Harvard "Shrink", 1992-1994 (Box Series III-4)
  - McCarthy, Paul: "Politicking and Paradigm Shifting: James E. McDonald and the UFO Case, 1976-1989; 2 folders (Box Series III-5)
  - McDonald, James E., 1953-1968; 2 folders (Box Series III-5)
    - Folder #1, 1953-1967 (Box Series III-5)
    - Folder #2, 1968 (Box Series III-5)
  - McIntyre, Williard F., 1978-1981 (Box Series III-5)
  - McNamara, Allen G.-Canadian National Research Council, 1979-1980 (Box Series III-5)
  - Mead, Margaret: "UFOs-Visitors From Outer Space?", 1974 (Box Series III-5)
  - Morrison, Nannette: Psychic / UFO Sighter, 1982-1983 (Box Series III-5)
  - Mysterious Crop Circles, 1987-1993 (Box Series III-5)
  - NATO UFO, 1977 (Box Series III-6)
  - NICAP: Misc., 1955-1978 (Box Series III-6)
  - Night-Talk: UFO Abductions, 18 June 1992, 1992-1993 (Box Series III-6)
  - NOVA: "Case of the UFOs," 1982, 1982-1983 (Box Series III-6)
  - Olmos, Vicente-Juan Ballester, "Alleged Exeriences Inside UFOs: An Analysis of Abduction Reports", 1994 (Box Series III-6)
  - Paul Harvey RV Show Incident, 1968 (Box Series III-6)
  - Pfeiffer-Life Magazine UFO Photographs, 1968-1974 (Box Series III-6)
  - Playboy Panel: UFOs, 1977 (Box Series III-6)
  - Project Starlight International (Ray Stanford), 1966-1979 (Box Series III-6)
  - Public Brainwashed by TV Movies on UFOs, 1974-1981 (Box Series III-6)
  - Rough, J. Edward: House Science and Astronatuics Committee, 1965-1969 (Box Series III-6)
  - Rutledge, Harley D.: S.E. Missouri State University, 1973-1976 (Box Series III-6)
  - "Spontaneous Human Combustion" Hoax; Steiger, Brad: "UFOs are Hostile", 1967-1968 (Box Series III-7)
  - Sanderson, Ivan, 1967-1970 (Box Series III-7)
  - South African "Crashed Saucer"1, 1980 (Box Series III-7)
  - South African Monoplane Hysteria, 1989 (Box Series III-7)
  - Spragatt, Allen: columns on "UFOs-Explained", 1975 (Box Series III-7)
  - Stalnaker, Lydia-UFO Psychic (Hugh Simpson), 1976-1985 (Box Series III-7)
  - Strentz, Herbert-"News Sources Used by Reporters in Writing Stories About Flying Saucer", 1970 (Box Series III-7)
  - Szasz, Thomas "The Lying Truths of Psychiatry", 1979 (Box Series III-7)
  - TV Documentary: "A Strange Harvest"-UFO Cow Mutilations, 1980-1983 (Box Series III-7)
  - UFO Abductions: Miscellaneous, 1985-1999 (Box Series III-7)
  - UFO Abductions: Newspaper Clippings, 1989-1996 (Box Series III-7)
  - UFOs-Indent. Source Material, 1961-1967 (Box Series III-7)
  - UFO: Newspaper Clippings-Miscellaneous (Box Series III-8)
    - UFO: Newspaper Clippings-Misc (Box Series III-8)
    - UFO: Newspaper Clippings-Misc, 1967-1972 (Box Series III-8)
    - UFO: Newspaper Clippings-Misc, 1973 (Box Series III-8)
    - UFO: Newspaper Clippings-Misc, 1974 (Box Series III-8)
    - UFO: Newspaper Clippings-Misc, 1975 (Box Series III-8)
    - UFO: Newspaper Clippings-Misc, 1976 (Box Series III-9)
    - UFO: Newspaper Clippings-Misc, 1983 (Box Series III-9)
    - UFO: Newspaper Clippings-Ohio, 1973 (Box Series III-9)
  - United Nations-UFO Activities, 1977-1979 (Box Series III-9)
  - United States: Phantom Airships, 1897, 1897-1977 (Box Series III-9)
  - United States Air Force: Air Base UFO Reports, 1976-1984 (Box Series III-9)
  - United States Air Force: Air Intel UFO Reports, 1950s-1960 # 1, 1957-1960 (Box Series III-9)
  - United States Air Force: Air Intel UFO Reports, 1950s-1960 # 2, 1957-1960 (Box Series III-9)
  - United States Air Force File: UFO Observation, 19 June 1968 (Box Series III-10)
  - University of Colorado-"Trick", 1966-1978 (Box Series III-10)
  - van Kampen, Hans-Holland UFOlogist, 1976-1977 (Box Series III-10)
  - Volunteer Flight Officers Network (VFON) and UFOs, 1963-1975 (Box Series III-10)
- Series IV. Strategic Defense Initiative (SDI) Files, 1957-1991; 4.5 lin. feet
  Material on the Strategic Defense Initiative (SDI) "Star Wars" program, and ballistic missile defense systems. Klass collected this material with the intention of writing a book on space weapons. The series is primarily comprised of newspaper and magazine articles, in addition to government publications. The series is arranged chronologically, with notable works in their own folder. Klass originally had these items arranged chronologically in binders. The original order has been maintained as much as possible. The only non-UFO material in the collection developed out of Klass' work at Aviation Week is the SDI material in Series IV. Klass began covering topics related to space defense weapons for the magazine in the late 1960s-anticipating an arms race in space. He proposed a book to his publisher Random House tentatively titled "Race to War in Space" in 1981 and was turned down. Klass had doubts at to the feasibility of creating a space defense system, and feared it would accelerate a space race. From 1981 to 1991 he continued to collect all available material on the subject in anticipation of writing a book until around 1987 when it became apparent that SDI was doomed. In addition, Klass was a long-time friend of Lt. General Jim Abrahamson who headed the Strategic Defense Initiative Organization.
  - SDI Material: 1957-Air University Quarterly Review, "The Air Force Ballistic Missile" (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1968-1970 (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1971 (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1972 (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1973 (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1974 (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1975 (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1976 (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1976 July 28, 29-"International Space Law" (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1976 October 7-10-"The Demilitarization of Outer Space" (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1976-Strategy for Peace Conference (17th), 1976 October (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1977 (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1977 October 13-16-"Problems of International Securityin Outer Space" (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1977 October 31-"Strategi Dynamics and Space-Laser Weapons" (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1977-Strategy for Peace Conference (18th), 1977 October (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1978 (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1978 July-Scoville, Jr., Herbert, "Can Space Remain a Peaceful Environment" (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1979 (Box Series IV-1)
  - SDI Material: 1980 (Box Series IV-2)
  - SDI Material: 1981 (Box Series IV-2)
  - SDI Material: 1982 (Box Series IV-2)
  - SDI Material: 1982 March-"Fiscal Year 1983 Arms Control Impact Statements" (Box Series IV-2)
  - SDI Material: 1982-Space Defense Systems Conference (Box Series IV-2)
  - SDI Material: 1983 January-April (Box Series IV-3)
  - SDI Material: 1983 May-August (Box Series IV-3)
  - SDI Material: 1983 September-December (Box Series IV-3)
  - SDI Material: 1983-Klass, Philip J., "Reagan's Star Wars" (Box Series IV-3)
  - SDI Material: 1984 January-April (Box Series IV-4)
  - SDI Material: 1984 March-Bunn, Matthew, "Technology of Ballistic Missile Reentry Vehicles" (Box Series IV-4)
  - SDI Material: 1984 May-August (Box Series IV-4)
  - SDI Material: 1984 August 24-Current News, "Strategic Defense Initiative" (Box Series IV-4)
  - SDI Material: 1984 September-November, Fall (Box Series IV-5)
  - SDI Material: 1984 September 10-Keyworth, II, G.A. "Technological Opportunities and National Security: A Global View" (Box Series IV-5)
  - SDI Material: 1984 December, n.d. (Box Series IV-5)
  - SDI Material: 1984 December 6-7, America Plans for Space (Space Symposium 1984) (Box Series IV-5)
  - SDI Material: 1984-Jastrow, Robert, "How to Make Nuclear Weapons Obsolete" (Box Series IV-5)
  - SDI Material: 1985 January-February, winter (Box Series IV-5)
  - SDI Material: 1985 March-April (Box Series IV-5)
  - SDI Material: 1985 May-July (Box Series IV-6)
  - SDI Material: 1985 June-"SDI A Technical Progress Report" (Box Series IV-6)
  - SDI Material: 1985 July 15-McNamara, Robert S., "Reducing the Risk of Nuclear War" (Box Series IV-6)
  - SDI Material: 1985 August-September, summer (Box Series IV-6)
  - SDI Material: 1985 September-"Ballistic Missile Defense Technologies" (Box Series IV-6)
  - SDI Material: 1985 October (Box Series IV-6)
  - SDI Material: 1985 October-"Soviet Strategic Defense Programs" (Box Series IV-6)
  - SDI Material: 1985 November-December (Box Series IV-6)
  - SDI Material: 1985 December 10-Payne, Keith B., "The Allies and the SDI" (Box Series IV-6)
  - SDI Material: 1985 December 10-"Statement on the Strategic Defense Initiative" (Box Series IV-6)
  - SDI Material: 1985-Department of Defense Appropriations for 1986, SDI (Box Series IV-6)
  - SDI Material: 1986 January-August (Box Series IV-7)
  - SDI Material: 1986 June-"Report to Congress on the Strategic Defense Initiative" (Box Series IV-7)
  - SDI Material: 1986 September-December (Box Series IV-7)
  - SDI Material: 1986 December 15-"Deployment of Missile Defenses in the 1990s" (Box Series IV-7)
  - SDI Material: 1986 Summer-"Policy Review Magazine" (Box Series IV-8)
  - SDI Material: 1986-"Weaponry in Space: the Dilemma of Security" (Box Series IV-8)
  - SDI Material: 1987 January-December (Box Series IV-8)
  - SDI Material: 1987 February 18-"Missile Defense in the 1990s-Technical Panel Study" (Box Series IV-8)
  - SDI Material: 1987 April-"Report to the Congress on the Strategic Defense Initiative" (Box Series IV-8)
  - SDI Material: 1987 April-"The Science and Technology of Directed Energy Weapons" Chp. 1-4 (Box Series IV-9)
  - SDI Material: 1987 April-"The Science and Technology of Directed Energy Weapons" Chp. 5-9, Appendix (Box Series IV-9)
  - SDI Material: 1987 April-Aftergood, Steven, "Nuclear Aspects of the Strategic Defense" (Box Series IV-9)
  - SDI Material: 1987 April 21-News briefing by Lt. Gen. James Abrahamson, USAF (Box Series IV-9)
  - SDI Material: 1987 September 21-"A Report to Congress on the Anitballistic Missile Treaty", 1987 April 21 (Box Series IV-9)
  - SDI Material: 1987 April 23-Briefing on APS Report (PJK Notes), 1987 September (Box Series IV-9)
  - SDI Material: 1987 June 19-"ASP Directed Energy Study Group Response to Critiques by Wood and Canavan", 1987 April 23 (Box Series IV-9)
  - SDI Material: 1987 November-Goldstein, Gary, "The Requirements for Ree Electron Laser Space Weapons", 1987 June 19 (Box Series IV-9)
  - SDI Material: 1987-Abrahamson and Sagan Debate the Strategic Defense Initiative, 1987 November (Box Series IV-9)
  - SDI Material: 1987-SDIO Comments on 1987 Report By APS (Box Series IV-9)
  - SDI Material: 1988 April-"Report to the Congress on the Strategic Defense Initiative", 1987 (Box Series IV-9)
  - SDI Material: 1989 May 11-"Statement on the Strategic Defense Initiative", 1988 April (Box Series IV-9)
  - SDI Material: 1991 February 12-"Briefing on the Refocused Strategic Defense Initiative", 1989 May 11 (Box Series IV-9)
  - SDI Material: n.d., 1991 February 12 (Box Series IV-9)
  - SDI Material: n.d.-Seitz, Frederick, "Comments on the Report of the American (Box Series IV-9)
  - SDI Material: n.d.-Wood, Lowell and Gregory Canavan, "Analysis of the APS Report on Directed Energy Weapons" (Box Series IV-9)
- Series V. Conferences and Symposia, 1968-1992; 0.5 lin. feet
  Published proceedings, transcripts, and related correspondence for UFO conferences. The series is arranged alphabetically, and then chronologically within each folder. Material and correspondence related to various UFO conferences. Published proceedings from the MUFON conferences have been transferred to the Library's Printed Materials department.
  - Abduction Study Conference-Cambridge, 1992, 1992 February-June (Box Series V-1)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science-Boston, 1969, 1968 July-1969 September (Box Series V-1)
  - MUFON Conference, 1987, 1987 June (Box Series V-1)
  - MUFON Conference, 1989 (Box Series V-1)
  - MUFON Conference, 1990 (Box Series V-1)
  - MUFON Conference, 1992 (?)-Linda Moulton Howe Slides (Box Series V-1)
  - Smithsonian UFO Symposium, 1980, 1970-1980 (Box Series V-1)
  - Smithsonian UFO Symposium, 1980-Transcript (Box Series V-1)
- Series VI. Periodicals, 1967-2000; 11 lin. feet
  UFO and SDI periodicals collected by Klass, as well as Klass's Skeptic UFO Newsletter (SUN). The series is arranged alphabetically by title, and then chronologically. The periodicals in Series VI range from single issues to complete runs of works published within the United States, as well as international works such as the German pro-UFO publication CENAP Report. Also in this series is Klass' own Skeptical UFO Newsletter which he began publishing on a bi-monthly schedule in 1989 and has attracted over 300 subscribers.
  - Abduction Watch, 1997-1998 (Box Series VI-1)
  - AFU Newsletter, 1989-1993 (Box Series VI-1)
  - American UFO Newsletter, 1997-1998 (Box Series VI-1)
  - Anomalies: L'Observateur des Pavasciences, 1996-1997 (Box Series VI-1)
  - Arms Control Today, 1986-1987 (Box Series VI-1)
  - Aura-z, 1993 (Box Series VI-1)
  - Aviation Week and Space Technology, 1981, 1986 (Box Series VI-1)
  - Bulletin of Anomalous Experience, 1990-1994 (Box Series VI-1)
    - Bulletin of Anomalous Experience, 1990-1992 (Box Series VI-1)
    - Bulletin of Anomalous Experience, 1993-1994 (Box Series VI-1)
  - Bulletin of the Intruders Foundation (Vol. 1), 1989-1992 (Box Series VI-1)
  - California UFO, 1986 (Box Series VI-1)
  - Cenap Report, 1990-1999 (Box Series VI-2)
    - Cenap Report, 1990-1993 (Box Series VI-2)
    - Cenap Report, 1994-1995 (Box Series VI-3)
    - Cenap Report, 1996-1997 (Box Series VI-4)
    - Cenap Report, 1998-1999 (Box Series VI-5)
  - C.E. Chronicles (1 issue Forbidden Science), 1993-1995 (Box Series VI-6)
  - Caveat Emptor, 1988-1990 (Box Series VI-6)
  - Cereologist: The Journal for Crop Circle Studies, 1990-1992 (Box Series VI-6)
  - Communion Letter, 1989-1991 (Box Series VI-6)
  - Contact Forum, 1993, 1995 (Box Series VI-6)
  - Continuum, 1991-1993 (Box Series VI-6)
  - Devil's Advocate, 1995-1997 (Box Series VI-6)
  - Enigmas, no date (Box Series VI-6)
  - Farout, 1992-1993 (Box Series VI-6)
  - Fate, 1992-1993 (Box Series VI-6)
  - Fortean Times, 1993, 1997 (Box Series VI-6)
  - Georgia Sky Watch, 1996 (Box Series VI-6)
  - Houston Sky, 1994-1996 (Box Series VI-7)
  - HUFON Report, 1993-1997 (Box Series VI-7)
  - International UFO Library Magazine, 1993 (Box Series VI-7)
  - International UFO Reporter, 1976-1998 (Box Series VI-7)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1976 (Box Series VI-7)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1977 (Box Series VI-7)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1978 (Box Series VI-7)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1979 (Box Series VI-7)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1980 (Box Series VI-7)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1981 (Box Series VI-7)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1982 (Box Series VI-7)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1983 (Box Series VI-7)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1984 (Box Series VI-7)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1985 (Box Series VI-8)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1986 (Box Series VI-8)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1987 (Box Series VI-8)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1988 (Box Series VI-8)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1989 (Box Series VI-8)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1990 (Box Series VI-8)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1991 (Box Series VI-8)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1992 (Box Series VI-8)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1993 (Box Series VI-8)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1994 (Box Series VI-8)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1995 (Box Series VI-9)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1996 (Box Series VI-9)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1997 (Box Series VI-9)
    - International UFO Reporter, 1998 (Box Series VI-9)
  - Journal fur UFO-Forschung, 1990 (Box Series VI-9)
  - Journal of Scientific Exploration, 2000 (Box Series VI-9)
  - Just Cause, 1978-1979 (Box Series VI-10)
  - Los Identificados, no date (Box Series VI-10)
  - Magonia, 1994-1998 (Box Series VI-10)
  - MUFON UFO Journal, 1980-1999 (Box Series VI-10)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1980 December (Box Series VI-10)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1981 (Box Series VI-10)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1982 (Box Series VI-10)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1983 (Box Series VI-10)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1984 (Box Series VI-11)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1985 (Box Series VI-11)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1986 (Box Series VI-11)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1987 (Box Series VI-11)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1988 (Box Series VI-11)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1989 (Box Series VI-12)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1990 (Box Series VI-12)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1991 (Box Series VI-12)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1992 (Box Series VI-12)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1993 (Box Series VI-13)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1994 (Box Series VI-13)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1995 (Box Series VI-13)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1996 (Box Series VI-13)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1997 (Box Series VI-14)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1998 (Box Series VI-14)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 1999 (Box Series VI-14)
    - MUFON UFO Journal, 2000 (Box Series VI-14)
  - NARO Minded, 1996, 1997 (Box Series VI-15)
  - New Ufologist, 1994-1996 (Box Series VI-15)
  - Oddysey, 1988-1990 (Box Series VI-15)
  - Official UFO, 1975 (Box Series VI-15)
  - Orbiter, 1989-1992 (Box Series VI-15)
  - Ovni Presence, 1992-1994 (Box Series VI-15)
  - Paradox, 1991-1992 (Box Series VI-15)
  - Perspectivas Ufologicas, 1993-1995 (Box Series VI-15)
  - Phenomena la revue des Phenomenes OVNI, 1992-1999 (Box Series VI-16)
    - Phenomena la revue des Phenomenes OVNI, 1992 (Box Series VI-16)
    - Phenomena la revue des Phenomenes OVNI, 1993 (Box Series VI-16)
    - Phenomena la revue des Phenomenes OVNI, 1994 (Box Series VI-16)
    - Phenomena la revue des Phenomenes OVNI, 1995 (Box Series VI-16)
    - Phenomena la revue des Phenomenes OVNI, 1996 (Box Series VI-16)
    - Phenomena la revue des Phenomenes OVNI, 1997 (Box Series VI-16)
    - Phenomena la revue des Phenomenes OVNI, 1998 (Box Series VI-16)
    - Phenomena la revue des Phenomenes OVNI, 1999 (Box Series VI-16)
  - Phoenix Newsletter, 1994-1996 (Box Series VI-16)
  - Roswell Reporter, 1994-1996 (Box Series VI-16)
  - Saucer News, 1967 (Box Series VI-16)
  - Saucer Smear, 1986-1998 (Box Series VI-16)
    - Saucer Smear, 1986 (Box Series VI-16)
    - Saucer Smear, 1987 (Box Series VI-16)
    - Saucer Smear, 1988 (Box Series VI-16)
    - Saucer Smear, 1989 (Box Series VI-17)
    - Saucer Smear, 1990 (Box Series VI-17)
    - Saucer Smear, 1991 (Box Series VI-17)
    - Saucer Smear, 1992 (Box Series VI-17)
    - Saucer Smear, 1993 (Box Series VI-17)
    - Saucer Smear, 1994 (Box Series VI-17)
    - Saucer Smear, 1995 (Box Series VI-17)
    - Saucer Smear, 1996 (Box Series VI-17)
    - Saucer Smear, 1997 (Box Series VI-17)
    - Saucer Smear, 1998 (Box Series VI-17)
  - Scienza and Paranormale, 1994 (Box Series VI-17)